<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    
    <title>LizardByte</title>
    
    
    <description>LizardByte</description>
    
    <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/</link>
    <atom:link href="https://app.lizardbyte.dev/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
      <item>
        <title>Sunshine v2025.122.141614 Released</title>
        <description>
          
          What’s Changed build(linux)!: remove legacy input option by @ReenigneArcher in #3562 fix(flatpak): fix broken desktop file, icons, and service by @ReenigneArcher in #3561 fix(web-ui): fix new version notification conditions by @ReenigneArcher in #3577 chore(l10n): update translations by @LizardByte-bot in #3563 New Contributors @CodyManess made their first contribution in #3558 Full...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 22 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-22-v2025.122.141614/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-22-v2025.122.141614/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Sunshine v2025.118.151840 Released</title>
        <description>
          
          Attention This release contains critical security updates. For more information see GHSA-3hrw-xv8h-9499. Please update as soon as possible! This release also contains many new features and bug fixes, including: Implemented automatic resolution and HDR mode changing on Windows. Implemented YUV 4:4:4 encoding support for Intel and NVIDIA GPUs on Windows....
        </description>
        <pubDate>Sat, 18 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-18-v2025.118.151840/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-18-v2025.118.151840/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Welcome</title>
        <description>
          to the blog of LizardByte! - 
          We’re thrilled to have you here. This blog is your go-to source for all the latest announcements, updates, and news about LizardByte projects. Whether you’re a developer, a tech enthusiast, or just curious about what we do, you’ll find valuable insights and information here. What to Expect Announcements: Stay updated...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Mon, 06 Jan 2025 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-06-welcome/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2025-01-06-welcome/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Autostart Sunshine on Boot without Auto-Login</title>
        <description>
          
          After following this guide you will be able to: Turn on the Sunshine host via Moonlight’s Wake on LAN (WoL) feature. Have Sunshine initialize to the login screen ready for you to enter your credentials. Login to your desktop session remotely, and have your pipewire audio and Sunshine tray icon...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Wed, 16 Oct 2024 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-10-16-autostart-sunshine-on-boot-without-auto-login/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-10-16-autostart-sunshine-on-boot-without-auto-login/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discord Call Cancellation in Sunshine on Windows</title>
        <description>
          Cancel Discord call audio with Voicemeeter (Standard) - 
          Voicemeeter Configuration Click “Hardware Out” Set the physical device you receive audio to as your Hardware Out with MME Turn on BUS A for the Virtual Input Windows Configuration Open the sound settings Set your default Playback as Voicemeeter Input Tip Run audio in the background to find the device...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Fri, 24 May 2024 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-05-24-discord-call-cancellation-sunshine-windows/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-05-24-discord-call-cancellation-sunshine-windows/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Discord Call Cancellation in Sunshine on Linux</title>
        <description>
          
          Set your normal Sound Output volume to 100% Start Sunshine Set Sound Output to sink-sunshine-stereo (if it isn’t automatic) In Discord, right click Deafen and select your normal Output Device. This is also where you will need to adjust output volume for Discord calls Open qpwgraph Connect sunshine [sunshine-record] to...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 18 Apr 2024 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-04-18-discord-call-cancellation-sunshine-linux/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-04-18-discord-call-cancellation-sunshine-linux/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Multi-platform C++ development in CLion</title>
        <description>
          How to set up CLion to handle Linux, macOS, and Windows development in a single project - 
          Introduction When developing multiplatform C++ projects, it can be frustrating to have to switch between different systems to develop, inspect, and test your code. This is especially true when you are working on a project that has dependencies. Without the proper setup, you may find your IDE complaining about missing...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Feb 2024 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-02-01-multi-platform-cpp-development-in-clion/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2024-02-01-multi-platform-cpp-development-in-clion/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Remote SSH Headless Sunshine Setup</title>
        <description>
          
          This is a guide to setup remote SSH into host to startup X server and Sunshine without physical login and dummy plug. The virtual display is accelerated by the NVidia GPU using the TwinView configuration. Attention This guide is specific for Xorg and NVidia GPUs. I start the X server...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 14 Sep 2023 00:00:00 -0400</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2023-09-14-remote-ssh-headless-sunshine-setup/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/2023-09-14-remote-ssh-headless-sunshine-setup/</guid>
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>Blog Guide</title>
        <description>
          
          Admonitions Usage You can use admonitions with the following syntax: {% include admonition.html type=&quot;important&quot; body=&quot;This is information intended to draw attention.&quot; %} Optionally, a custom title can be added: {% include admonition.html type=&quot;hint&quot; title=&quot;Custom Title&quot; body=&quot;This is information intended to draw attention.&quot; %} Types Valid types of admonitions are: attention...
        </description>
        <pubDate>Thu, 01 Jan 1970 00:00:00 -0500</pubDate>
        <link>https://app.lizardbyte.dev/1970-01-01-blog-guide/</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">https://app.lizardbyte.dev/1970-01-01-blog-guide/</guid>
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
